https://www.toypost.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy & Cookies Privacy We are committed to protecting your privacy and only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). All personal information is held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law. Customers who tick the ‘send newsletter’ box when placing an order may receive latest news or promotions from time to time relating to Toypost. Customers may also receive an email invitation to subscribe to a newsletter. If you do not wish to receive any newsletters or promotions, simply ignore the invitation. You can inform us at any time to delete your details from our files. Cookies What are cookies? Cookies are small text files that are saved to your computer. Toypost uses cookies to remember users during a visit and are required to enable certain functionality within the site. In addition, cookies are used to help us understand how our customers use our websites and we use this information to help plan improvements to the site. Toypost does not use cookies to collect or store personally identifiable information about you. A new EU Directive (2009/136/EC) came into force on 26 May 2011, changing the way in which websites use cookies and gain consent from users. We are currently working on ways in which our website will be updated to support these new rules. Below are details of how we currently use cookies. How do we use cookies? Both Toypost and third parties make use of cookies when you visit our websites. The following is a description of the types of cookies that are used, why they are used and details of the individual cookies. Sessions: Session cookies are used by us to recognise a user throughout a visit. This enables us to remember information that you have entered, for example, the product you have selected during a purchase which can then be used at each stage of processing your purchase. Session cookies are also used to remember you when you log in for the duration of your visit. Marketing: Cookies enable us to identify which type of advertising results in sales. This means that we are able to tailor our marketing more effectively. Website analytics: Website analytics enables us to see how people use our website. This gives us the information to be able to make improvements, to make the site easier to use and based on the areas of the site people find most useful. Website optimisation: We test different versions of parts of the site before we finalise changes to ensure that any improvements make the site easier to use for our customers. Cookies help us to track how a user progresses through sections of the website that we are testing.
Facebook-f
Twitter
Instagram
Terms and Conditions
Contact Us
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Policy
Terms and Conditions
This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website. More Info
